jamesmillerlifeology.com 2019-12-11

# ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY AGREEMENT — James Miller | Lifeology™

James Miller | Lifeology, (James Miller | Lifeology), is committed to keeping any and all personal information collected of those individuals that visit our website and make use of our online facilities and services accurate, confidential, secure and private. Our privacy policy has been designed and created to ensure those affiliated with James Miller | Lifeology of our commitment and realization of our obligation not only to meet but to exceed most existing privacy standards.

THEREFORE, this Privacy Policy Agreement shall apply toJames Miller | Lifeology and any subsidiary company listed below , and thus it shall govern any and all data collection and usage thereof. Through the use of [https://www.JamesMillerLifeology.com](https://www.jamesmillerlifeology.com/) and any subsidiary website listed below you are herein consenting to the following data procedures expressed within this agreement.

Subsidiary Company: Subsidiary Website: [Lifeology.tv](http://lifeology.tv/)

### Collection of Information

This website collects various types of information, such as:

  * Voluntarily provided information which may include your name, address, email address, 

billing and/or credit card information etc., which may be used when you purchase products and/or services and to deliver the services you have requested.

  * Information automatically collected when visiting our website, which may include cookies, third party tracking technologies and server logs. 

Please rest assured that this site shall only collect personal information that you knowingly and willingly provide by way of surveys, completed membership forms, and emails. It is the intent of this site to use personal information only for the purpose for which it was requested and any additional uses specifically provided on this site.

James Miller | Lifeology may have the occasion to collectanonymous demographic information, such as age, gender, household income, political affiliation, race and religion at a later time.We may also gather information about the type of browser you are using, IP address or type of operating system to assist us in providing and maintaining superior quality service.

It is highly recommended and suggested that you review the privacy policies and statements of any website you choose to use or frequent as a means to better understand the way in which other websites garner, make use of and share information collected.

### Use of Information Collected

James Miller | Lifeology may collect and may make use of personal information to assist in the operation of our website and to ensure delivery of the services you need and request. At times, we may find it necessary to use personally identifiable information as a means to keep you informed of other possible products and/or services that may be available to you from https://www.JamesMillerLifeology.com and our subsidiaries . James Miller | Lifeology and our subsidiaries may also be in contact with you with regards to completing surveys and/or research questionnaires related to your opinion of current or potential future services that may be offered.

James Miller | Lifeology does not now, nor will it in the future, sell, rent or lease any of our customer lists and/or names to any third parties.

James Miller | Lifeology may deem it necessary to follow websites and/or pages that our users may frequent in an effort to gleam what types of services and/or products may be the most popular to customers or the general public.

James Miller | Lifeology may disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, only if required to do so in accordance with applicable laws and/or in a good faith belief that such action is deemed necessary or is required in an effort to:

  * Remain in conformance with any decrees, laws and/or statutes or in an effort to comply with any process which may be served upon James Miller | Lifeology and/or our website;
  * Maintain, safeguard and/or preserve all the rights and/or property ofJames Miller | Lifeology; and
  * Perform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of users of https://www.JamesMillerLifeology.com and/or the general public.

### Children Under Age of 13

James Miller | Lifeology does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13) without verifiable parental consent. If it is determined that such information has been inadvertently collected on anyone under the age of thirteen (13), we shall immediately take the necessary steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our system’s database. Anyone under the age of thirteen (13) must seek and obtain parent or guardian permission to use this website.

### Unsubscribe or Opt-Out

All users and/or visitors to our website have the option to discontinue receiving communication from us and/or reserve the right to discontinue receiving communications by way of email or newsletters. To discontinue or unsubscribe to our website please send an email that you wish to unsubscribe to info@jamesmillerlifeology.com. If you wish to unsubscribe or opt-out from any third party websites, you must go to that specific website to unsubscribe and/or opt-out.

### Links to Other Websites

Our website does contain links to affiliate and other websites.James Miller | Lifeology does not claim nor accept responsibility for any privacy policies, practices and/or procedures of other such websites. Therefore, we encourage all users and visitors to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. The aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement applies only and solely to the information collected by our website.

### Security

James Miller | Lifeology shall endeavor and shall take every precaution to maintain adequate physical, procedural and technical security with respect to our offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of the user’s personal information under our control.
